<resources>
    <string name="app_name">C.E.G.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Center for Electronic Governance</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_home">homeActivity</string>

    <string name="title_activity_courses">All Courses</string>
    <string name="cpp_activity_name">C++ Programming Lnaguage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <dimen name="text_size">18sp</dimen>
    <dimen name="image_text_size">25sp</dimen>

    <string name="cpp_text">

        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "

        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"
        "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"
        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"




    </string>
    <string name="about_course_cpp">
        WELCOME TO CEG

        1.cpp is a object oriented language.\n
        2.seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n
        3.technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.
        4.technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.
        5.technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.
        5.jfjnfjbgvjbfbhjbgevbfvkjvb.
    </string>

    <string name="about_course_cpp1">
        WELCOME TO CEG

        roshan
    </string>
    <string name="prerequesite_android">
       Basic knowledge of Java programming and androids. Beginners are also welcome.
    </string>
    <string name="about_android">
        Android Development is the process by which new applications are created for
        devices running the Android
        operating system. Officially, apps can be written using Java, C++ using the Android studio.
    </string>
    <string name="android_include">
         Duration: 60 Days
         Course fee: 7000.00 Rs.
    </string>
    <string name="android_description">
        Java concepts Basic, Application Structure (in detail), Emulator and Intents,
        Basic UI design, Styles and Themes, Dialog boxes, Images and media, Composite, Server Connection,
        Fragments, Google Maps, Location based Services, Accessing Phone services etc.
    </string>

    <string name="android_what_i_learn">
        Students will learn skills for creating and deploying Android applications,
        with particular emphasis on software engineering topics including
        software architecture, software process, usability, and deployment. You’ll learn how to create an Android project with Android Studio and run a debuggable version of the app.
        You'll also learn some Android architecture and the key principles underlying its design.

    </string>
    <string name="prerequesite_ml">
       Basic knowledge of  programming and androids. Beginners are also welcome.
    </string>
    <string name="about_ml">
        This course provides a broad introduction to machine learning,
        data mining, and statistical pattern recognition. Topics include:\n
        (i) Supervised learning \n
        (ii) Unsupervised learning\n
        (iii) Best practices in machine learning\n
    </string>
    <string name="ml_include">
         Duration: 60 Days\n
         Course fee: 11000.00 Rs.\n
         Live project:Yes\n
    </string>
    <string name="ml_description">
        Machine learning is a subset of artificial intelligence in the field of computer science that often
        uses statistical techniques to give computers the ability to "learn"
        progressively improve performance on a specific task with data, without being explicitly programme.
    </string>

    <string name="ml_what_i_learn">
        Through this highly rigorous and selective PG Diploma program we will help you to learn:
      Learn Classification Algorithms, Deep Learning, NLP, Reinforcement Learning and Graph Models
       Create intelligent solutions such as Chatbots, Smart Games and Image Classifiers

    </string>



</resources>
